by my dad which is a good thing since
time is limited
how was he asked to provide personal
insight describing why I think he
deserves this award I'm not having a lot
of time and a lot of stories to tell
either but it's easy for me to answer
why he deserves to work this
organization was established to
recognize individuals who have made
available and lasting contribution to
our multicultural city and region and to
inspire a new generation of leaders I
went that my dad is receiving this award
because he's done the anymore from the
time he came here as an international
student from a country thousands of
miles away not knowing the language very
well until today when he's received more
proclamations citations and recognitions
but I can account for helping people
he's demonstrated again and again his
commitment to helping others and
improved our society the professionalism
he's shown as enhance the reputation of
the Lebanese community in everyone's
eyes he's one respected for experience
and impartiality as was his father
before him and was for his example I
learned experience love of our heritage
civic mindedness love of God over family
and love of our great country he's a
Renaissance man in peacemaking has been
a pretty service man trust to love these
but our entire community you know I'm a
statistics dinner
then in our country for 25% of its
history one 1/4 the night states we get
here and we're all better off for it
I'm proud to be your son and I think the
people their natural hollow thing for
recognizing them this evening ladies and
gentlemen mr. other than that